A lot of people think that.
The evidence is there.
The evidence is all there.
It's, it's, come on, we spend, we send $18 million a year to Israel.
Why?
Just ask the question, what do we get out of it?
Nothing.
We get nothing.
Are we doing humanitarian work?
No other charge with genocide.
They're killing off Palestinians.
Are we helping them survive?
Well, they've got a higher standard to live than we do, a longer lifespan than we do.
Free education, free housing, free healthcare, or we're sending them money.
Why?
Ask yourself why a U.S. congressman can wear an Israeli military uniform in congressional
chambers.
I would think that would be an act of treason.
But they did.
Nobody said anything.
Ask why the Israeli prime minister can bypass the president, fly directly in and speak to
our congress without any other government interaction.
I didn't know that could happen.
Oh yeah.
Netanyahu did, flew straight in bypass the president, talked to the Congress.
Congress gave him 26 standing ovations.
I think most pop stars would like 26 standing ovations.
Our Congress gave Netanyahu a foreign prime minister 26 standing ovations.
I have difficulty looking at that.
In any other way, then, we're occupied.